

SUJAN THAPA

Bhanu-05, Tanahun - Nepal +977 9843544732, sujanthapamagar960@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a motivated and enthusiastic person aiming to set my mind and work towards it. After my graduation I joined a purpose-driven project in mySecondTeacher.com which has served millions of students through its web and mobile platform. Besides this I have sharpened my analytical and research skills while working with some personal projects. Nowadays, technology is advancing, due to which there will be more things to learn. I believe by pursuing higher education I will be able to master the latest technologies in inter-cultural teams.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021 BSc (Hons) Computing

Islington College (London Metropolitan University)

Kamalpokhari, Kathmandu

2015 - 2017 NEB Board (High School)

Nepal Police Secondary Boarding School, Kavrepalanchok

2015 School Level Certification (SLC)

Pashchim Kshetriya Prahari Awasiya Ma Vi Belchautara, Tanahun

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2019 September - 2019 December

Empathy IT Club

Internship

• Practical implementation of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and MySQL database.

1 March 2021 - 28 February 2022

Innovate Tech Pvt. Ltd.

Trainee

Innovate Tech Pvt. Ltd.

1 March 2022 - Present

Content Ingestion Officer

- Responsible for overseeing subject operation.
- Sessions establishment on trends of new technology.
- Provided training and motivational sessions to intern groups.
- Communicate within the team members about requirements, challenges and deadlines.
- Monitoring to ensure that requirements are not off track.

SKILLS

- Web Application Development
- Mobile Application Development
- Programming languages
- Collaborative work on google sheets/docs
- Proofread and quality check online content for errors and fixing
- Microsoft Office

LANGUAGES

- Nepali
- English

REFERENCES

Samujjwal Pandey	Ashok Dhungana	Kriti KC
Ingestion Officer, Innovate Tech	Senior Lecturer, BSc (Hons) in	Manager, Student Services
Pvt Ltd.	Computing	Islington College Pvt Ltd
Email:	Email:	Email:
samujjwal.pandey@innovatetec	ashok.dhungana@islingtoncolle	kriti.kc@islingtoncollege.edu.np
h.co	ge.edu.np	